Guide to the Duke Endowment Archives, 1902-2018 and undated, bulk 1925-2006 RL.00332
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Audiovisual Materials Series (RESTRICTED), 1991-1995 and undated, 3 boxes
  - Audiocassette Subseries
    Recordings of miscellaneous meetings and addresses pertaining mainly to the Health Care and Child Care Divisions Series. Arranged chronologically.
    [Restrictions note: Originals are closed to use; however, use copies are available.]
    - Originals (CLOSED) (Box AV 1)
      - OR1A-C. 1991 May 22, Plenary Session, 18th Rowland Library Health Planning Seminar (TRT unknown), 3 copies (Box AV 1)
      - OR2. 1992 Apr. 12-14, Leland R. Kiser, Creating Healthier Communities: The Challenge for the 21st Century, The Healthcare Forum, Anaheim, California (TRT Unknown) (Box AV 1)
      - OR3. 1995 May 3-4, Keynote Address By: Russell C. Coile, Jr, Rowland Library Health Planning Seminar, Omni Charlotte Hotel (TRT unknown) (Box AV 1)
      - OR4. Undated, Janet Sarbon, and Bill Strickland, Expert Briefing/Arts: A Multi Dimensional Experience (TRT unknown) (Box AV 1)
    - Preservation Copies (CLOSED) (Box AV 2)
      - PC1-PC4 (Box AV 2)
    - Use Copies (RESTRICTED) (Box AV 3)
      - UC1-UC4 (Box AV 3)
- Oversize Materials (RESTRICTED)
  - Treasurer's Office Series, 1989
    - Form 990 Reports, supporting materials, 1989 (Oversize-box 36)
  - Controller's Office Series, 1924-1928
    - Miscellaneous Subseries, 1924-1928
      - Worksheet: Reallocation of Income-A, 1924-1928 (Oversize-box OM 1)
      - Worksheet: Reallocation of Income-B, 1924-1928 (Oversize-box OM 1)
  - Health Care and Child Care Divisions Series, 1925-1926, 1971
    - Hospital and Child Care: Statistics (maps), North Carolina and South Carolina, 1925-1926 (Oversize-folder OC:V:5)
    - Hospital Statistics, 1971, 2 copies (Oversize-box 36)
  - Rural Church Division Series, 1930-1977 and undated
    - Building Grant Files Subseries, 1930-1977 and undated
      - Blueprints and Plans: (Oversize-folder OC:V:1)
        - Amity Church - Buxton Church, 1955-1971 and undated (Oversize-folder OC:V:1)
        - Campground Church - Duke's Chapel, 1942-1967 and undated (Oversize-folder OC:V:1)
        - Ebenezer Church - Etowah Church, 1961-1967 and undated (Oversize-folder OC:V:1)
        - Fairgrove Church - Groomtown Church, 1958-1965 and undated (Oversize-folder OC:V:2)
        - Hallsboro Church - Kenly Church, 1959-1975 and undated (Oversize-folder OC:V:2)
        - Lake Waccamaw Church - McBride Church, 1958-1969 and undated (Oversize-folder OC:V:2)
        - Macedonia Church - Mount Hermon Church, 1930-1969 and undated (Oversize-folder OC:V:2)
        - Mount Moriah Church - North River Church, 1949-1968 and undated (Oversize-folder OC:V:2)
        - Oak Forest Church - Patton Church, 1947-1969 and undated (Oversize-folder OC:V:2)
        - Pikeville Church - Pittsboro Church, 1938-1968 and undated (Oversize-folder OC:V:2)
        - Pleasant Grove Church - Providence Church, 1930-1967 and undated (Oversize-folder OC:V:3)
        - Rainbow Church - Royal Oaks Church, 1961-1967 (Oversize-folder OC:V:3)
        - Saint Andrew's Church - Saint Timothy's Church, 1960-1967 and undated (Oversize-folder OC:V:3)
        - Salem Church - Shiloh Church, 1961-1977 and undated (Oversize-folder OC:V:3)
        - Siloam Church - Sunshine Church, 1956-1968 and undated (Oversize-folder OC:V:3)
        - Tabernacle Church - Verona Church, 1961-1968 and undated (Oversize-folder OC:V:3)
        - Watha Church - Zion Church, 1957-1967 and undated (Oversize-folder OC:V:3)
    - Miscellaneous Subseries, 1962-1975 (Oversize-folder OC:V:5)
      - Committees on Church Architecture
        - Randolph E. DuMont Design Program, blueprints and plans, 1962-1975, 3 folders (Oversize-folder OC:V:5)
  - Publications Series, 1931
    - Child Care Division: (Oversize-box 36)
      - A System of Accounting for Children's Homes, Bulletin No. 2, Revised, 1931 Jan. (Oversize-box 36)
  - Trust Under Will Series, 1926-1961
    - Analysis of Income and Expenses, 1926-1961 (Oversize-box 23)
    - Analysis of Expenses--Current, 1937-1942 (Oversize-box 23)
    - Accounting: Working Papers for 1933 Distribution, 1933-1934 (Oversize-box 23)
  - Miscellaneous Series, circa 1920-1970 and undated
    - James B. Duke 100th Anniversary Programs, 1956 Dec. 11 (Oversize-box 36)
    - Pictures, People:
      - Allen, George Garland, undated (Oversize-box 36)
      - Duke University Trustees, circa 1940s (Oversize-box 36)
      - Perkins, Thomas L., undated (Oversize-box 36)
    - Pictures, Places:
      - Duke University, West Campus:
        - circa 1932-1935 (Oversize-box 36)
        - circa 1932-1935 Aerial view of campus, undated (Oversize-box 36)
        - Chapel, circa 1932-1935 (Oversize-box 36)
    - Architectural Drawings, The Duke Endowment: (Oversize-folder OC:V:4)
      - Durham Office, proposed changes; M.W.M Middleton, Wilkerson, McMillan, Architects, 1963, 1970 (Oversize-folder OC:V:4)
    - Architectural Drawings, Duke University, West Campus:
      - Addition to library building, Office of Horace Trumbauer, 1946 (Oversize-folder OC:V:4)
      - Buildings, Horace Trumbauer, Architect, undated, 2 folders (Oversize-folder OC:V:4)
      - General Grading Plans, Olmstead Brothers, 1931; General (Oversize-folder OC:V:4)
      - Plans, Horace Trumbauer, Architect, 1926-1933 (Oversize-folder OC:V:4)
      - Plans showing proposed new buildings, Horace Trumbauer, Architect, circa 1920s (Oversize-folder OC:V:4)
      - Plot Plans, Office of Horace Trumbauer, 1930-1940 (Oversize-folder OC:V:4)
    - Architectural Drawings, Duke University Hospital:
      - Drawings and Plot Plan for addition, Office of Horace Trumbauer, 1953 (Oversize-folder OC:V:4)
      - Drawings and Floor Plans, Office of Horace Trumbauer, 1960 (Oversize-folder OC:V:4)
      - Sketch and Floor Plan, 1938 (Oversize-folder OC:V:4)
    - Awards: Certificate honoring the Trustees of the Duke Endowment for establishing the Bennette Eugene Geer Chair in Literature, Furman University, 1996 (Oversize-box 36)
    - Maps of Duke University, 1945-1948; Map of Forest Cover of Durham Division-Duke Forest, 1944 (Oversize-folder OC:V:4)
    - Pictures:
      - Power Stations: Cliffside Station, Spartanburg, S.C., circa 1940 (Oversize-folder OC:V:4)
      - Cowans Ford Dam and Lake Norman, 1964 (Oversize-folder OC:V:4)
      - Riverbend Station, Catawba River, N.C., circa 1940 (Oversize-folder OC:V:4)
    - Thomas L. Perkins: Certificates, diploma, license, 1942-1952 (Oversize-box OM 1)